Finding Aid of the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Office of the Director Records, 1885-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1885-2014, UWM Archival Collection 10; 28.6 cubic ft. (49 boxes, including 15 audio reels, 16 audio cassettes, and 23 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder
  - Colloquium, 1968-1980 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Columbia Hospital, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Commemorating the Acquisition of the One Millionth Volume, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Committee on Automated Library Services, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Committee on Government Documents, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Institutional Development, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Reprography, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Complaints, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Computer Center, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Conzen Lecture
    - 1985 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Holzheimer Series, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Coon, Arthur M., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Research Projects, circa 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence
    - 1979-1988 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 1999 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Barczyk, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Watson-Boone, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 3-6)
    - Watson-Boone, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - Cost of Catalog, circa 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Crawford Lecture, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Cruz Cano Map, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Cultural and Technological Studies, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cultural Map of Wisconsin Forum, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Curriculum Collection
    - 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 1979-1988 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Curriculum Library
    - 1955-1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Circulation, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Guides 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - History, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Memos, 1956-1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Scrapbook, 1955-1961 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - Custodial Staff Appreciation Reception, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - CUWL Joint Meeting, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Data Base Services, 1975-1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Dante's Sinful Lovers, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Davies, Robertson, Friends of the Library Speech, 4 June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Davies, Robertson, Friends of the Library Speech, 4 June 1976, Audio reel (¼ in., 7 ½ ips) (Box 13, Audio 4)
  - Dayan, Yael, Remarks, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Delia Ovitz Memorial, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Department of English, 1962-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Department of Hebrew Studies, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Department of Planning and Development, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Departmental Libraries, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Departmental Requests, 1959-1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Dial Access System, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dilke Lecture, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - DIN, 1990-1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Dinerstein, I. A., 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Displays and Exhibits, 1958-1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Division of Urban Outreach, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Donations from Golda Meir Library, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Don Quixote Reference Slide Tape, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Drazniowsky, Roman, Farewell, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Dublin, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - E159, 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Educational Communications Division, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Educational Technology
    - 1997-2002 (Box 49, Folder 10-14)
    - Final Report, 1996-1999 (Box 49, Folder 15-17)
  - Ehlers Middle East Program, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Elementary Reference Library Withdrawal Book, 1931-1950 (Box 20)
  - Elshoff, Gerhard J., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Emergencies, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Environmental Information Center, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Endowment Campaign, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Equipment Lists, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-1989, Library Administrative Group, Executive Cabinet (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee Recommendations, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Exhibits and Lectures, Brochures, 1964-1989, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Exhibits Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Expanded Database, Educational Technology, 1997-1998 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Extension Division, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Publications, 1973-1981 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Status for Librarians, 1971-1981 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Time Utilization, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 5th Anniversary of the Library Building and the Acquisition of the 1 Millionth Item, Audio cassette (Box 27, Audio 10)
  - Film Distribution Department, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - First Edition, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - First Friday, 1987-1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Five-Year Review, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Floor Plan Review, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Forman, Harrison Information, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Forms Used at the State Normal School Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Founders Day - Black History, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Frank Zeidler's Guide to Resource Persons on Milwaukee Culture, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - French Map Exhibit, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Friends of the Golda Meir Library
    - 1958-1965 (Box 5, Folder 1-7)
    - 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 1983-1995 (Box 40, Folder 63-72)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Agendas, Minutes, Membership, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Announcements, 1963-1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, 1983-1995 (Box 41, Folder 3-15)
    - Annual Meeting and Program, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Board Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Book Sale
      - 1983-1997 (Box 41, Folder 17-20)
    - By-Law Revision, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - By-Laws, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Center for Twentieth Century Studies Program, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Dinner, 1978-1982 (Box 41, Folder 24-25)
    - Dinner Speech, 10 June 1977, Audio reel (¼ in., 7 ½ ips) (Box 13, Audio 5)
    - European Tour, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Friends Event, "Beyond the Facade", 1989 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Friends News, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Program, "When Toys Were Tin", 1989 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Reception, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Logo Contest, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Meetings, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Membership, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Membership Lists, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Miscellanous Old Records, 1976-1985 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - News Releases, 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter
      - 1997 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - 2005 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - 2004-2014
        Records captured as part of UWM Web Collection.
    - Organization
      - 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - 1978 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - 1982 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Program Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Program Ideas, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Programs in Progress, 1994-1997 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Treasurer, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Uecker Program, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Valentine Program, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Frink, Miriam, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Fromkin Family Correspondence, 1971-1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Fromkin Oral History Project, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Fromkin Room, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Gamaliel Program, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Gapen Colloquium, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Gaston's War, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Gatteno, Holzhuetes, 1984-1994 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - German Consul, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Gifts, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Goethe Exhibit, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Golda Meir Collection Project, 1979-1991 (Box 48, Folder 1-5)
  - Golda Meir Library Construction Negatives, undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Golda Meir Library Dedication and Guides, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Golda Meir Library Newsletter
    - 1974-1992 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - 1993-2005 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Gormley, Mark M., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Gottmann, Jean
    - Action at Crossroads, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 54)
    - Megalopolis, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Graduate School, 1977-1997 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Guides, Miscellaneous
    - 1962-1972 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 1974-1999 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Handbook Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Handicapped Access, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Handmade Paper Workshop, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Hard Hat Party, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Hardie Aerospace Collection, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Hardie Conference, Wisconsin Aviation, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Hardie Event, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Harkey Lecture, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Harley, Brian, Cartography, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Harley, John Memorial, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Harley Lecture, Aztec World, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Harrasowitz, Otto, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Harris, Chauncy
    - 1987 (Box 41, Folder 63)
    - Reception, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Henderson Collection, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Herriott, Homer, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Herta Nottleman's Retirement Party, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Hiberia-Irelande-Eire: Images of Ireland, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hispanic History and Culture Conference, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Historical Chronology, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - History of the Library, 1885-1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Hoffman, Frederick J., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Hoffman-Scher, Lecture, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Hohlweck, Civil War Collection
    - 1985 (Box 41, Folder 68)
    - 1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Hohlweck, Civil War Roundtable, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Holiday Card, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Holzheimer Lecture, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 70-72)
  - Holzheimer Lecture, "Maps and America", 2001, 3 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 44, Video 5-7)
  - Holzheimer Lecture, "The U.S. Geological Survey", 1999, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 44, Video 4)
  - "How the West Was Mapped", 2001 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Howard Stern Memorial Fund, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Identification Cards, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - IMC News Notes, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Incipit, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Information and Media Technology, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Undergraduate Library Education, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Instructional Technology, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Interlibrary Loan
    - 1956-1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - 1984-1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - International Conference on Cartography, American Geographic Society Visit, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - International Federation of Library Associations, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Irish Bibliography, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Irish Cultural Institute, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Irish Harp Program, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Irish Program, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Irish Studies Program, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Irving, Washington, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Israel: War and Peace, with Amos Oz, 1997, 1 Videocassette (VHS) (Box 44, Video 3)
  - Item Record Task Team, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Italian Oral History Collection, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Jackson Slide Talk and Brunch, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Jeansonne Program, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Jeffrey Stone African Lecture, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Jewish Book Month, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Jewish Community 150th Year Program, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Jewish Literature Symposium, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Jews and Arabs in Medieval Spain, Friends Program, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - Johnson Controls Grant, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Josey, E.J.
    - 1987 (Box 41, Folder 88)
    - Friends Reception, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 89)
    - Talk, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - Joyce/Woolf Night, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - Kenwood Library, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Klotsche Dinner Committee, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Klotsche, J. Martin, 1951-1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Komsi, William, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Kraus Periodicals, Inc., 1963-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Krawcyk China Talk, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - Krawcyk Event, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - Kulisiewicz, Alexandr, Archives Proposal, Music, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Kwasniewski, Roman B.J., Collection, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Labor Relations, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Language and Area Center, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Laskin, Myron, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Lawrence University, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Layton Collection, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - Librarians' Cabinet Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Librarians Reception, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - Libraries for Milwaukee Lectures, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - Library Administrative Committee, 1971-1988, Library Administrative Group, Executive Committee (Box 6, Folder 15-19)
  - Library Administrative Group Agendas and Minutes
    - 1997-2002, Library Administrative Committee, Executive Committee (Box 41, Folder 97-101)
    - 2001-2007, Library Administrative Committee, Executive Committee (Box 42, Folder 1-5)
  - Library Anniversary, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Library Announcements and Events, 1977-1990 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Library Associates
    - 1964 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Library Automation, NLS and Notis, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 14-15)
  - Library Automation Speech, Epstein, Audio cassette (Box 27, Audio 11)
  - Library Automation at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Library Building Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Library Building Plan Committee, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Library Construction, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Library Cooperation Group, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Library Decorating Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Library Dedication
    - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - 1987 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Clippings File, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Library Department Heads Committee, 1964-1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Library Executive Committee
    - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 27-28)
    - Documents, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Minutes, 1975-1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Library Fundraising and Endowments, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Library Guides, 1962-1967 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Library Handbook, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Library History, 1973-1979 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Library Institute, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Library Map, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Library Movers and Consultants, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Library Objectives, 1963-1974 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Library of Congress, 1930-1961 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Library Planning Study Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Library Publicity, 1977-2003 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Library Review Audit, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Library Systems Planning Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Library Tours, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Library Use Survey, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lincoln Avenue Calendars, 1993-1997 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln's Religion, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Linden Grove Dedication, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Lydolph Colloquium, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lydolph Festschrift, Letters, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Lydolph Festschrift (Soviet Geography Studies), 1988 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Mac Nab Program, Sailing, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Machacek Talk, Center for Twentieth Century Studies, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Madison Library Visit, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Maher "Hamlet" Lecture, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Mann, Sally, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Maps and Colombian Encounter, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Maps of Holy Land, Les Jongleurs
    - 1984 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - 1988 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Maps of the Columbian Encounter Videotape, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Maps of the Middle East Videotape, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Maya Cave Paintings, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Mayer Geography Lectures, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Media Advisory Committee
    - 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 40-42)
    - Consultants Visit, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Media Distribution, 1973-1982 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Media Services
    - Annual Reports, 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Media Utilization Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Medical Library Resource Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Meir Benefit Concert, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Menashri Talk, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Merger, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Meyer Collection Architectural Journals and Omnion Wind Power, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Meyers Music Collection Program, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Microlab, Ribbon Cutting, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Midwest Academic Librarians Conference, 1957-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Midwest Inter-Library Center, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Midwest Library Network, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Midwest Parent-Child Welfare Resource Center, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Milton Tercentenary, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Milwaukee County Law Library Task Force, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Milwaukee-Downer College, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Milwaukee Initiative II, 1993-1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Milwaukee Peace Education Foundation, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Milwaukee Public Library, 1957-1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Milwaukee" Sculpture, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Minert Collection, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, A-W, 1944-1967 (Box 7, Folder 16-30)
  - Modern Languages Association, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Moebius Award
    - 1983-1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Publicity, 1983-1993 (Box 42, Folder 33-41)
  - Money Gifts, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Morley, Charles, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Morris Fromkin Lecture Series
    - 1970-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1-26)
    - 1972, Audio reel (¼ in., 5 ips) (Box 13, Audio 15)
    - 1974, Audio cassette (Box 27, Audio 23)
    - 1975-1977, 3 Audio reels (¼ in., 7 ½ ips) (Box 13, Audio 16-18)
    - 1978-1980, 3 Audio reels (¼ in., 7 ½ ips) (Box 33, Audio 19-21)
    - 1980, 2 Audio cassettes (Box 27, Audio 24-25)
    - 1982, Audio reels (¼ in., 7 ½ ips) (Box 33, Audio 22)
    - 1983-1986, 4 Audio cassettes (Box 27, Audio 26-29)
    - 1988, 2 Audio cassettes (Box 27, Audio 30-31)
    - 1990-1991, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 42-45)
    - 1993-2007, 16 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 44, Video 8-23)
    - 1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
    - Acknowledgements, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Background, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Book I, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Brochure, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Invitations, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Posters
      - 1971-2009 (Oversize 1)
      - 1978-1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Publicity, 2002-2006 (Box 49, Folder 20-21)
    - Quest for Social Justice, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Quinn, Lois, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Symposium, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Morris, William, Exhibit, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Movietonews, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Mueller Memorial, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Music Collection, 1979-1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Music Library, 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Naming of Golda Meir Library, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Nash, John, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Native American Program, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Native American Studies Library Committee, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Nelson Lecture, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - News Releases, 1968, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - NHPRC Grant Proposal, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Niemz Talk, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Nimitz, Maxine, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - NLS System
    - 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - NLS User's Guide, 4th Ed., 1993 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - NLS/NOTIS
    - 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Planning Meeting, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Non-Book Materials Committee, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Northwest Ordinance, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - NOTIS, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - NTIS Microfiche, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - O'Lochlainn, Colon, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Olson, Frederick I., 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Omsk Drama, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - One Millionth Volume, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Order Preparation Task Team, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Order Procedures, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Order Processing Task Team, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Organizational Charts, 1964-1979, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Otness, Guidebook Program, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Owens Jazz Collection, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Oz, Amos, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Parent-Teacher Library Accession Book, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Peace Corps, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Perline, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Photographs
    - A Celebration of Intellect: Books by UWM Authors, undated (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Exhibition in AGS, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Golda Meir Library
      - Exterior, 196?-197? (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Exterior Construction, 1965-1980s (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Interior, 1960s-1970s (Box 32, Folder 33-34)
      - Interior Construction, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Student Staff, undated (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Kwasniewski Processing, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Mellencamp Library, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Physical Plant, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Planning Document
    - 1981 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 24-25)
    - 1986-1991 (Box 26, Folder 26-27)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 28-29)
    - 1989 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 31-34)
  - Planning Task Force on Computing, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Plans, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - PM Ballet, Friends, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Policy Statements, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Polish Bicentennial, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Polish Countryside: Louise Boyd Exhibit and Program, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Polish Microfilm Project, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Postnikov Lecture, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Preservation Unit, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 55-56)
  - Procedures Manual
    - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6-14)
  - Professional Development Committee
    - 1976-1990 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Professional Development Program, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Program Requirements for the Library at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Programs, Retrospective, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Prospective Donor Information, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Provost, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Pulaski Day Program, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Purchasing Office, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Rare Books Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Reading Between the Lines, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Receipt of Materials Task Team, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Red Riding Hood, Zipes Program, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Reference Department Meetings, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)